A Finding Aid to the Gloria Ross Papers, circa 1924-1998, in the Archives of American Art AAA.rossglor
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, circa 1924-1990s; Series 8; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 11, 16
  - Frankenthaler Family, circa 1924-1930s (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gloria Ross Tapestries, circa 1966-1990s (Box 11, Folder 9-13)
    Oversized material housed in Box 16, Folder 5
  - Gloria Ross Tapestries, Negatives, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Gloria Ross Tapestries, Transparencies, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 15-19)
  - Edinburgh Tapestry Company, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Navajo Rugs, 1986; 1993 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Navajo Weavers, 1990; 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Navajo Weavings, circa 1980s (Box 11, Folder 23-24)
  - Pinton Atelier, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Robert Halperin House, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Tapestries, Victorian Tapestry Workshop, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Various Weaving Workshops, Negatives, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Exhibition Opening, Denver Art Museum, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Tapestries at Denver Art Museum, circa 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Tapestries At Denver Art Museum, Transparencies, circa 1991 (Box 11, Folder 31-32)
  - Calder Tapestries, Slides, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Slides, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Oversized Photograph Album, Tapestry Workshops, circa 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Photograph Album, Gloria Ross Tapestries, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Photograph Album, Gloria Ross Tapestries, circa 1970s (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Oversized Photographs, Gloria Ross Tapestries from Box 11, Folders 9-13, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Artwork, circa 1970s-1990s; Series 9; 1.1 Linear feet Boxes 11-14, 17, 19
  Artwork of note includes a small painted canvas by Paul Jenkins. Additional artwork includes color swatches, yarn, and unidentified textile samples, most likely created for collaborative projects with painters. Researchers should note that many other identified drawings and textile samples are included in Series 3: Project Files.
  - Paul Jenkins, Painting on Canvas, circa 1970s (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Textile Samples, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 12, Folder 1-4)
  - Textile Samples, circa 1970s (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Oversized material housed in Boxes 14 and 19
  - Yarn Samples, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Oversized Artwork Color Samples, circa 1970s (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Textile Samples from Box 13, Folder 1, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Textile Samples from Box 13, Folder 1, circa 1970s-1990s (Box 19)